export const Round1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"Name the Trial comparing Oral semaglutide  to empagliflozin, where primary endpoint was change in HbA1C from baseline to week 26.",
    options: ["Pioneer2","Pioneer3","SUSTAIN2","SUSTAIN3"],
    correctAnswer: "Pioneer2",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"Name the Trial  where semaglutide delays the progression of renal impairment and lowers the risk of renal and cardiovascular mortality in subjects with type 2 diabetes and chronic kidney disease. ",
    options: ["Sustain6","PIONEER6","FLOW","SOUL"],
    correctAnswer: "FLOW",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"Both PIONEER 6 and SUSTAIN 6 are ______ _______ for semaglutide molecule both oral and injectable",
    options: ["Preapproval CVOT","Postapproval CVOT","Event and time driven"],
    correctAnswer: "Preapproval CVOT",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    level: 100,
    type: 3,
    question:"the main organ contributing to Rybelsus weight loss is…..",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "BRAIN",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"SUSTAIN 10 trial was to compare the efficacy and safety of semaglutide 1mg vs ________ in adults with T2D.",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "Liraglutide 1.2mg",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  }, {
    id: 6,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"A prospective, non-interventional study, investigating the use of once-daily oral semaglutide in type 2 diabetes patients who intend to fast during Ramadan in real-world setting. ",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "O-Sema-FAST",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  }, {
    id: 7,
    level: 200,
    type: 1,
    question:"In FLOW trial OW semaglutide s.c. 1.0 mg demonstrated _____ first composite kidney event, and this was the primary kidney endpoint. ",
    options: ["24%RRR","26%RRR","36%RRR","18%RRR"],
    correctAnswer: "24%RRR",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    level: 200,
    type: 3,
    question:"the biggest challenge addressed by Rybelsus is…..",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "FEAR OF INJECTION, PREFERENCE OF ORAL",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  }, 
  {
    id: 9,
    level: 200,
    type: 1,
    question:"In SUSTAIN 6 the risk of nephropathy was _______ lower with semaglutide vs placebo ",
    options: ["36% significantly","36%nonsignificant","24% significant","24% non-significant"],
    correctAnswer: "36% significantly",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  
  {
    id: 10,
    level: 200,
    type: 3,
    question:"If you skip a dose of Ozempic more than …. Days, you need to skip the weekly dose and take the next dose on the scheduled day.",
    options: ["3","4","5","7"],
    correctAnswer: "5",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    level: 200,
    type: 1,
    question:"In PIONEER 3, Oral semaglutide14mg showed significant HbA1C and wt reduction vs sitagliptin in week 26 by ______ and _________respectively ",
    options: ["(-1.3%, -3.1kg)","(-1.2%, -3.5kg)","(-1.4%, -3.6kg)","(-1.5%,3.8kg)"],
    correctAnswer: "(-1.3%, -3.1kg)",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    level: 200,
    type: 1,
    question:"OW semaglutide s.c. 1.0 mg demonstrated ________ risk reduction of MACE in FLOW trial ",
    options: ["significant 18% RRR","NS 16 % RRR","significant 26% RRR","NS 26% RRR"],
    correctAnswer: "significant 18% RRR",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    level: 300,
    type: 1,
    question:"In SUSTAIN 4, OW semaglutide 0.5 mg showed significant HbA1C and wt reduction vs insulin glargine by ______ and _________ respectively",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "(-1.2%, -3.5KG)",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    level: 300,
    type: 3,
    question:"In Rybelsus CLM: Describe the patient profile of Sarah.  (age, BMI, other co-morbidities, medication)",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "YOUNG AGE, EARLY DIABETES JOURNEY, HTN and DYSLIPIDEMIA, BMI ABOVE 30",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    level: 300,
    type: 1,
    question:"Subjects in both semaglutide treatment arms experienced significantly more weight loss compared with placebo: Weight reduction of 3.7 kg and 4.5 kg with semaglutide 0.5 mg and 1.0 mg, respectively in ",
    options: ["PIONEER 1","SUSTAIN 9","SUSTAIN 5","SUSTAIN 1"],
    correctAnswer: "SUSTAIN 1",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    level: 300,
    type: 3,
    question:'In RYBELSUS CLM: What does the "Y" represent in RYBELSUS READY patients?',
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "yet to require a medication with CV risk reduction",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    level: 300,
    type: 3,
    question:"Percentage of Patients in PIONEER REAL, who found Rybelsus easy or very easy to use.",
    options: ["75%","80%","85%","95%"],
    correctAnswer: "85%",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    level: 300,
    type: 1,
    question:"First non-fatal stroke was one of the components of the primary endpoint in PIONEER 6 where HR was ______ for semaglutide vs placebo",
    options: ["1.18","0.74","0.56","0.49"],
    correctAnswer: "0.74",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  // Add more questions here
];
